<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ten_guy">ten Guy  also known as  \"Really High Guy \" and  \"Stoner Stanley \"  is an advice animal image macro series featuring a photo of a young man who appears to be under the influence of marijuana. The captions typically portray stereotypical stoner behavior, similar to Stoner Dog, such as giving invalid answers to misunderstood questions and craving junk food.</string>
    <string name="advice_dog">Advice Dog is a popular image macro series that features a picture of the head of a smiling puppy on a multicolored color wheel background split into 6 colors. Usual derivatives are often accompanied by two lines of text written in a guidance \ advising format with the advice given usually being very poor, unethical or deplorable.  Since its debut, the series has spawned dozens of spin-offs referred to as Advice Animals of an animal\'s head on a color wheel background or merely just an animal (including humans) with their own archetype personalities using the same two line image macro formula.</string>
    <string name="advice_god">Advice God is an advice animal image macro series featuring a portrait of an old man with grey hair and a long flowing beard. The images are typically captioned with text that denounces religion (often christianity) by pointing out apparent biblical contradictions and attributing mischievous behaviors to God.</string>
    <string name="ancient_aliens"> Ancient Aliens is a series of image macros based on History Channel\'s TV series with the same name starring alien expert Giorgio A. Tsoukalos, who often tends to explain inexplicable phenomena as the direct result of aliens or extraterrestrials being on Earth. In a somewhat similar fashion to Bill O\'Reilly\'s You Can\'t Explain That series, the Ancient Aliens macros exaggerate Tsoukalos\' beliefs to such an extent that they become humourous.
</string>
    <string name="annoying_childhood_friend"> Annoying Childhood Friend is an advice animal image macro series featuring a photo of a young boy in a white polo shirt smiling at the camera. Like a younger version of Scumbag Steve, the captions typically portray the character as an inconsiderate host, a demanding guest or an obnoxious playmate.
</string>
    <string name="annoying_facebook_girl">Annoying Facebook Girl is an advice animal image macro series featuring a photo of a teenage girl rolling her eyes with her mouth agape, accompanied by a blue and white color wheel background. The overlaid text typically depicts vapid status updates, attention whoring and generally irritating Facebook activity.
</string>
    <string name="anti_joke_chicken">Anti-Joke Chicken is an image macro series featuring an image of a hen accompanied by a top line of text that sounds like the introduction of a joke, but the bottom line provides an unexpected anticlimax. The chicken is centered within a typical advice animal starburst background.
</string>
    <string name="art_student_owl">Art Student Owl is an advice animal image macro series featuring an owl with a cigarette in its mouth. The overlaid text typically makes fun of art student stereotypes or conveys frustrations commonly shared by artists and students in art school.
</string>
    <string name="baby_godfather">Baby Godfather is an image macro series featuring a scowling baby dressed in a tuxedo with a bow-tie pointing to the ground with his index finger. The captions typically portray the baby as an infant version of Don Corleone, a fictional mafia boss character in Mario Puzo\'s novel and Francis Coppola\'s film adaptation The Godfather.
</string>
    <string name="bad_advice_cat">Bad Advice Cat is an advice animal image macro series with a cat recommending terrible or inane solutions to life\'s problems, similar to Advice Dog.
</string>
    <string name="bad_joke_eel">Bad Joke Eel is an advice animal image macro series featuring a close-up photograph of a Moray eel with various captions delivering unfunny puns and jokes, very similar to Lame Pun Coon.
</string>
    <string name="bad_luck_brian">Bad Luck Brian is an image macro series featuring a photo of a blonde teenage boy wearing a plaid sweater vest and braces, accompanied by captions that describe a variety of embarrassing and tragic occurrences.
</string>
    <string name="bear_grylls">\"Bear Grylls \" is an image macro series featuring a photo of Edward  \"Bear \" Grylls, the host of UK\'s wildlife survival series Born Survivor, also known as Man vs. Wild in the US, Canada, Australia and New Zealand. While some macros use captions parodying the ridiculous and oftentimes unnecessary stunts Grylls performs on the show, they typically focus on the consumption of his own urine.
</string>
    <string name="brace_yourselves">Imminent Ned (also know as  \"Winter is Coming \") is an image macro series featuring the character Eddard  \"Ned \" Stark from the HBO series Game of Thrones, a television adaption of George R. R. Martin\'s epic fantasy novel series A Song of Ice and Fire. Its snowclone template  \"Brace Yourselves, X is Coming \" can be versatilely used to forewarn or proclaim the impending arrival of a highly anticipated event, a product or an internet meme.
</string>
    <string name="business_cat">Business Cat is an advice animal image macro series featuring a cat in a tie in front of a starburst background. The overlaid text usually includes something an office boss would do or request, but with a feline twist.
</string>
    <string name="butthurt_dweller">Butthurt Dweller, also known as  \"Gordo Granudo \", is an image macro series that features a photo of a young adult male with a ponytail and glasses accompanied by overlaid text that involves a smug or judgmental statement.
</string>
    <string name="chemistry_cat">Chemistry Cat (sometimes known as Science Cat) is an advice animal image macro series which consists of a scientific pun and a picture of a cat with a bow-tie and glasses sitting in front of a board. These puns are usually based on the names of chemical elements from the periodic table or various laws of science and physics.
</string>
    <string name="college_freshman">College Freshman (a.k.a Uber Frosh) is an image macro series featuring a college student with headphones, a University New Hampshire hoodie and a mobile phone. Portrayed as a hybrid of Scumbag Steve and Socially Awkward Penguin, the captions usually highlight the all-too-familiar cliches found in campus social scenes and student life during college years.
</string>
    <string name="conspiracy_keanu">Conspiracy Keanu is an advice animal image macro series featuring a still photo of the Hollywood actor Keanu Reeves wearing a frightened expression from the\'89 comedy film Bill and Ted\'s Excellent Adventure. The images are typically captioned with paranoid conjectures and absurdly philosophical questions that bear similarities to the Paranoid Parrot, Philosoraptor and Stoner Dog advice animal series.
</string>
    <string name="computer_guy">Computer Reaction Faces are reaction face images used to express the emotions of someone sitting in front of a computer screen, which often take the form of comic illustrations and animated GIFs.
</string>
    <string name="confession_bear">Confession Bear is an advice animal image macro series featuring a photo of a Malayan sun bear leaning against a log. The images are captioned with confessions about taboo behaviors and controversial opinions that are often kept secret for fear of being ostracized.
</string>
    <string name="courage_wolf">Courage Wolf is an image macro series derived from the original Advice Dog series. In contrast to Advice Dog, who might unknowingly lead you to do something you\'ll regret, Courage Wolf will help you achieve greatness with often extreme, overwhelming advice.
</string>
    <string name="crazy_girlfriend_praying_mantis">Crazy Girlfriend Praying Mantis is an advice animal image macro series featuring a photo of a praying mantis set against a blue and teal colorwheel background. The overlaid text typically describes what an overbearing, irrational or obsessive girlfriend might say to her significant other.
</string>
    <string name="creepy_condescending_wonka">Condescending Wonka is an advice animals image macro series featuring a screen capture of actor Gene Wilder in the\'71 musical Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory. As its name suggests, the captions can be characterized as patronizing and sarcastic.
</string>
    <string name="depression_dog">Depression Dog is an advice animal style image macro featuring a cut out photo of a taxidermic dog on color wheel background with shades of gray. The captions typically present bleak situations with a downtrodden outlook, similar to Forever Alone image macros.
</string>
    <string name="downvoting_roman">Downvoting Roman \ Commodus Thumbsdown is an Advice Animal style image macro series featuring a stillshot of actor Joaquin Phoenix[1] as Emperor Commodus in the 2000 epic film Gladiator. The image depicts a stone-faced Commodus giving a thumbs down and the overlaid text usually conveys dissatisfaction towards a post on a website or forum where a voting system is present, especially on Reddit.
</string>
    <string name="drunk_baby">Drunk Baby is an advice animal image macro series featuring a photograph of an infant sitting next to a pint of beer. The captions typically portray the baby as an intoxicated storyteller mimicking the behavior of older bar patrons.
</string>
    <string name="dwight_schrute">Schrute Facts is an image macro series inspired by Dwight Schrute, a character from the American version of the TV sitcom The Office. The overlaid text typically begins with an idiom or common belief, followed by a refutation of the aforementioned idiom based on a rationalist interpretation similar to buzzkill humor.</string>
    
</resources>
